[
    {
        "question_index": 1,
        "question_text": "The woman made toast for breakfast. What did she use?",
        "correct_answer": "b. bread",
        "other_options": [
            "a. oranges",
            "c. eggs",
            "d. milk"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 2,
        "question_text": "The children went to the zoo Saturday. What did they see?",
        "correct_answer": "a. monkeys",
        "other_options": [
            "b. tennis",
            "c. cartoons",
            "d. comedies"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 3,
        "question_text": "He had to cut the grass yesterday. Where did he work?",
        "correct_answer": "b. in the yard",
        "other_options": [
            "a. in the mill",
            "c. in the office",
            "d. in the shop"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 4,
        "question_text": "He is a new student. When did he arrive?",
        "correct_answer": "c. recently",
        "other_options": [
            "a. suddenly",
            "b. carefully",
            "d. usually"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 5,
        "question_text": "This is a manufacturing town. Where do most of the people work?",
        "correct_answer": "b. in a factory",
        "other_options": [
            "a. on a farm",
            "c. in a hotel",
            "d. in a restaurant"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 6,
        "question_text": "Mr. Brown is a respectable person. How would you describe him?",
        "correct_answer": "c. He has a good reputation.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He has a lot of money.",
            "b. He is poor.",
            "d. He is healthy."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 7,
        "question_text": "The artist’s fame is international.",
        "correct_answer": "d. He is famous all over the world.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He is famous all over town.",
            "b. He is famous throughout the area.",
            "c. He is famous throughout the country."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 8,
        "question_text": "The students enjoy ice cream.",
        "correct_answer": "a. They like it.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. They buy it.",
            "c. They sell it.",
            "d. They make it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 9,
        "question_text": "Mary is on vacation.",
        "correct_answer": "b. She doesn’t have to go to work.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. She is feeling bad.",
            "c. She is working harder.",
            "d. She is working overtime."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 10,
        "question_text": "Three people followed me last night.",
        "correct_answer": "d. They were behind me.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. They laughed at me.",
            "b. They injured me.",
            "c. They called me."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 11,
        "question_text": "During the baseball season, my wife and I enjoyed the games on TV.",
        "correct_answer": "a. We watched the games.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. We played the games.",
            "c. We got tired of them.",
            "d. We took pictures of them."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 12,
        "question_text": "Mary is very pretty. How does she look?",
        "correct_answer": "c. attractive",
        "other_options": [
            "a. happy",
            "b. friendly",
            "d. rich"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 13,
        "question_text": "The only painting I liked cost fifty dollars. Each of the others was half that price. What was\nthe price of the other paintings?",
        "correct_answer": "a. $25.00",
        "other_options": [
            "b. $50.00",
            "c. $75.00",
            "d. $100.00"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 14,
        "question_text": "There were many customers in the store. What was in the store?",
        "correct_answer": "b. people who buy things",
        "other_options": [
            "a. things for sale",
            "c. people who work at the store",
            "d. counters for holding goods"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 15,
        "question_text": "Where do you normally see clouds?",
        "correct_answer": "c. in the sky",
        "other_options": [
            "a. in the garden",
            "b. on the sea",
            "d. on the ground"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 16,
        "question_text": "John will coordinate the controls. What will he do to the controls?",
        "correct_answer": "a. He will make them operate together.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. He will leave them alone.",
            "c. He will color them.",
            "d. He will repair them separately"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 17,
        "question_text": "Is your air conditioner automatic?",
        "correct_answer": "c. Yes, it goes on and off by itself.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. Yes, it is well built.",
            "b. Yes, it is very old.",
            "d. Yes, it is manually controlled."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 18,
        "question_text": "Many people who live in this area are engaged in farming. What do they do?",
        "correct_answer": "b. grow vegetables",
        "other_options": [
            "a. repair automobiles",
            "c. make movies",
            "d. sell tractors"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 19,
        "question_text": "Some accidents occur in heavy traffic. Where do some accidents occur?",
        "correct_answer": "c. on crowded streets",
        "other_options": [
            "a. on the open highway",
            "b. on small bridges",
            "d. in small garages"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 20,
        "question_text": "Peter asked Carol about the stuff on the table. What did he ask about?",
        "correct_answer": "a. the things",
        "other_options": [
            "b. the time",
            "c. the weather",
            "d. the news"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 21,
        "question_text": "My eyes are weak.",
        "correct_answer": "d. I can’t see very well.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. I can see very well.",
            "b. I have good vision.",
            "c. I have strong eyes."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 22,
        "question_text": "The old man likes to sleep in the afternoon.",
        "correct_answer": "c. He sleeps after lunch.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He sleeps when it is dark.",
            "b. He sleeps before breakfast.",
            "d. He sleeps when it is cold."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 23,
        "question_text": "The children will slide on the ice.",
        "correct_answer": "d. They will slip.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. They will sit.",
            "b. They will fight.",
            "c. They will talk."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 24,
        "question_text": "The president of a company has the authority to change working hours.",
        "correct_answer": "a. He has the power.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. He has the excuse.",
            "c. He has the time.",
            "d. He has the money."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 25,
        "question_text": "Sergeant Brown said, “May I leave for town at eight?” The instructor said yes.",
        "correct_answer": "b. Sgt Brown can leave at eight.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. Sgt Brown left for town.",
            "c. The instructor will not let him go.",
            "d. Sgt Brown doesn’t want to go."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 26,
        "question_text": "A fireman must not wear flammable clothing.",
        "correct_answer": "b. His clothing must be fireproof.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. His clothing must be in fashion.",
            "c. His clothing must not be brand new.",
            "d. His clothing must not be a red color."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 27,
        "question_text": "Mike did his work with care.",
        "correct_answer": "d. Mike is a good worker.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. Mike was the first to finish.",
            "b. Mike tied his work together.",
            "c. Mike is very old."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 28,
        "question_text": "Jonas came by ship.",
        "correct_answer": "b. He arrived on a ship.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He looked at a ship.",
            "c. He went past a ship.",
            "d. He walked up to a ship."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 29,
        "question_text": "Jane lives in Evanston, which is a suburb of Chicago. Where does Jane live?",
        "correct_answer": "b. close to Chicago",
        "other_options": [
            "a. close to Evanston",
            "c. in the center of Chicago",
            "d. in neither Evanston nor Chicago"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 30,
        "question_text": "He was looking for a familiar landmark. What was he looking for?",
        "correct_answer": "d. a landmark he could recognize",
        "other_options": [
            "a. a landmark that was large",
            "b. an odd-shaped landmark",
            "c. an unusual landmark"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 31,
        "question_text": "Which is a fluid?",
        "correct_answer": "b. water",
        "other_options": [
            "a. fire",
            "c. a car",
            "d. a water pipe"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 32,
        "question_text": "Dave told us to bring the sports equipment. What did Dave tell us to bring?",
        "correct_answer": "a. the bats and the balls",
        "other_options": [
            "b. the tickets for the games",
            "c. the baseball team",
            "d. the sports instructor"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 33,
        "question_text": "The tail of the airplane was damaged. What part of the airplane was damaged?",
        "correct_answer": "a. the rear",
        "other_options": [
            "b. the left side",
            "c. the front",
            "d. the top"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 34,
        "question_text": "Particles of wood were found in the oil. What was found in the oil?",
        "correct_answer": "a. small pieces of wood",
        "other_options": [
            "b. one piece of wood",
            "c. something like wood",
            "d. large chunks of wood"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 35,
        "question_text": "They finally reached the peak.",
        "correct_answer": "a. They got to the top.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. They learned the truth.",
            "c. They made a decision.",
            "d. They finally gave up."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 36,
        "question_text": "He distributed the newspapers to the students.",
        "correct_answer": "a. He gave a newspaper to each student.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. He gave all the newspapers to one student.",
            "c. He showed the newspapers to the students.",
            "d. He read the newspapers to the students."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 37,
        "question_text": "Sandra wants to be a pilot. But her parents want her to be an engineer. She always obeys\nher parents.",
        "correct_answer": "b. Sandra is going to be an engineer.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. Sandra prefers engineering.",
            "c. Sandra is going to be a pilot.",
            "d. Sandra’s parents want her to be a pilot."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 38,
        "question_text": "He was sure he could pass the test.",
        "correct_answer": "a. He knew he could pass it.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. He hoped he could pass it.",
            "c. He wanted to pass it.",
            "d. He didn’t think he could pass it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 39,
        "question_text": "Mrs. Barnett caught the bus.",
        "correct_answer": "b. She was in time for the bus.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. She was too late for the bus.",
            "c. She was waiting for the bus.",
            "d. She was asking for the bus."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 40,
        "question_text": "He is willing to travel.",
        "correct_answer": "b. He is agreeing to travel.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He is refusing to travel.",
            "c. He is forced to travel.",
            "d. He is afraid to travel."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 41,
        "question_text": "The man’s wound was fatal.",
        "correct_answer": "d. He died.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He needed a bandage.",
            "b. He needed a nurse.",
            "c. He rested."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 42,
        "question_text": "The store put a number of things on sale. What did they do?",
        "correct_answer": "b. lowered the price",
        "other_options": [
            "a. put them outside",
            "c. kept prices the same",
            "d. stopped selling"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 43,
        "question_text": "That regulation is not applicable to this situation.",
        "correct_answer": "b. It can’t be used.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. It can’t be trusted.",
            "c. It can’t be explained.",
            "d. It can’t be determined."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 44,
        "question_text": "Adam took up Spanish.",
        "correct_answer": "d. He started to learn Spanish.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He failed to learn Spanish.",
            "b. He preferred to speak Spanish.",
            "c. He appeared to know Spanish."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 45,
        "question_text": "My grandmother needs to take a snooze.",
        "correct_answer": "c. She’ll go to sleep.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. She’ll go shopping.",
            "b. She’ll go to town.",
            "d. She’ll go walking."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 46,
        "question_text": "Ten new words appeared on the test. Ester missed four of them. How many did she get\ncorrect?",
        "correct_answer": "c. six",
        "other_options": [
            "a. four",
            "b. ten",
            "d. fourteen"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 47,
        "question_text": "Sergeant James gave his captain his reason for being late. What did Sgt. James tell him?",
        "correct_answer": "c. why he was late",
        "other_options": [
            "a. how he got there",
            "b. when he would be late",
            "d. where he was going later"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 48,
        "question_text": "We must de-emphasize war. What must we do?",
        "correct_answer": "b. make war less important",
        "other_options": [
            "a. make war less expensive",
            "c. make war less dangerous",
            "d. make war less destructive"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 49,
        "question_text": "What did your roommate wear to the party?",
        "correct_answer": "c. He had on a dark suit.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He left at 8 o’clock.",
            "b. He went with a friend.",
            "d. He went to the officer’s Club."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 50,
        "question_text": "Jack carried out the order. What did he do?",
        "correct_answer": "d. He executed it.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He canceled it.",
            "b. He destroyed it.",
            "c. He threw it away."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 51,
        "question_text": "The sailor can steer that small boat.",
        "correct_answer": "d. He can guide it.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He can get in it.",
            "b. He can put water in it.",
            "c. He can take pictures of it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 52,
        "question_text": "Frank couldn’t afford to get a new car.",
        "correct_answer": "c. He didn’t have enough money to get a new car.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He couldn’t get interested in a new car.",
            "b. He couldn’t decide about getting a new car.",
            "d. He didn’t want to get a new car."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 53,
        "question_text": "We succeeded because we had determination.",
        "correct_answer": "c. We didn’t give up.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. We were not interested.",
            "b. We made excuses.",
            "d. We needed motivation."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 54,
        "question_text": "The foreign student had to get used to the new customs.",
        "correct_answer": "c. He had to adjust to the customs.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He had to find out about the customs.",
            "b. He had to organize the customs.",
            "d. He had to disregard the customs."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 55,
        "question_text": "That company has a reputation for being above board. The company is       .",
        "correct_answer": "b. trustworthy",
        "other_options": [
            "a. exorbitant",
            "c. fraudulent",
            "d. successful"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 56,
        "question_text": "Phyllis went to the beverage section of the grocery store. She wanted to buy some .",
        "correct_answer": "c. soft drinks",
        "other_options": [
            "a. bread",
            "b. bacon",
            "d. green beans"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 57,
        "question_text": "W: Does your teacher give you lots to do after class? M: Sometimes, but she didn’t last night.\nThe teacher sometimes gives him _____.",
        "correct_answer": "homework",
        "other_options": [
            "comfort",
            "grades",
            "credit"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 58,
        "question_text": "W: What hurts?   M: My ear.   He has ____.",
        "correct_answer": "an earache",
        "other_options": [
            "a stomachache",
            "a headache",
            "a backache"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 59,
        "question_text": "W: Did you begin in November? M: Yes, and I finished in one month.  When did the man\nfinish?",
        "correct_answer": "December",
        "other_options": [
            "January",
            "June",
            "October"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 60,
        "question_text": "W: How will you get your dog to take that medicine?  M: I’m going to inject it.  What’s the\nman going to do with the medicine?",
        "correct_answer": "He’s going to give the dog a shot.",
        "other_options": [
            "He’s going to throw it away.",
            "He’s going to make the dog eat it.",
            "He’s going to cover the dog with it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 61,
        "question_text": "M: Which are the main chapters of the book?  W: The third and fourth.  What do we know\nabout the third and fourth chapters?",
        "correct_answer": "They are the most important.",
        "other_options": [
            "They are the shortest.",
            "They are the dullest.",
            "They are the most difficult"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 62,
        "question_text": "W: Is this alright?  M: I don’t know. We need to measure it first.  What does the man want to\ndo first?",
        "correct_answer": "find out how big it is",
        "other_options": [
            "keep it safe",
            "open it up",
            "find out what it is"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 63,
        "question_text": "M: What happened to Erica?  W: She lost her voice.  What was wrong with Erica?",
        "correct_answer": "She couldn’t sing.",
        "other_options": [
            "She couldn’t read.",
            "She couldn’t hear.",
            "She couldn’t see."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 64,
        "question_text": "M: I’m looking for an article on preventative medicine.  W: Here’s one in this magazine.\nWhat was the man doing?",
        "correct_answer": "searching for an article",
        "other_options": [
            "wait for an article",
            "planning to write an article",
            "reading an article"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 65,
        "question_text": "W: He collects rocks from all parts of the world.  M: That’s nice, but do they have any value?\nWhat does the man want to know?",
        "correct_answer": "Are they worth anything?",
        "other_options": [
            "Are the rocks unusual?",
            "Are they different shapes?",
            "Are they hard to find?"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 66,
        "question_text": "W: What did Tom do when the water bill came?  M: He got kind of riled.  Tom was ____.",
        "correct_answer": "mad",
        "other_options": [
            "injured",
            "happy",
            "wet"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 67,
        "question_text": "I  dinner now.",
        "correct_answer": "a. am eating",
        "other_options": [
            "b. eating",
            "c. ate",
            "d. had eaten"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 68,
        "question_text": "Select the correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "c. The gas tank will hold 16 gallons.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. The gas tank will 16 gallons hold.",
            "b. The gas tank 16 gallons will hold.",
            "d. The 16 gallons gas tank will hold."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 69,
        "question_text": "Select the correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "c. Can you tell us how to operate this system?",
        "other_options": [
            "a. How to operate this system can you tell us?",
            "b. Can you tell us this system how to operate?",
            "d. How to operate this system tell us can you?"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 70,
        "question_text": "This book is the same as that one.",
        "correct_answer": "c. identical to",
        "other_options": [
            "a. different from",
            "b. next to",
            "d. near"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 71,
        "question_text": "Tom bought a gallon of .",
        "correct_answer": "c. milk",
        "other_options": [
            "a. butter",
            "b. eggs",
            "d. cheese"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 72,
        "question_text": "Give me something for my headache.  I need      .",
        "correct_answer": "d. some medicine",
        "other_options": [
            "a. a hat",
            "b. some advice",
            "c. some food"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 73,
        "question_text": "The vegetables were fresh.  They were       .",
        "correct_answer": "a. direct from the garden",
        "other_options": [
            "b. frozen",
            "c. direct from storage",
            "d. dehydrated"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 74,
        "question_text": "Adam wasn’t able to go with us.",
        "correct_answer": "a. He couldn’t go.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. He didn’t want to go.",
            "c. He wasn’t ready to go.",
            "d. He wasn’t supposed to go."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 75,
        "question_text": "Last night, unfortunately, the team forfeited the game because they begin without\ntheir coach.",
        "correct_answer": "b. couldn’t",
        "other_options": [
            "a. can’t",
            "c. shouldn’t",
            "d. mustn’t"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 76,
        "question_text": "They’re planning on the trip tomorrow.",
        "correct_answer": "a. to leave",
        "other_options": [
            "b. be leaving",
            "c. leaving",
            "d. will leave"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 77,
        "question_text": "Select the correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "a. The teacher went quickly into the school at 8:30 a.m.",
        "other_options": [
            "b. The teacher into the school went quickly at 8: 30 a.m.",
            "c. The teacher went quickly at 8: 30 a.m. into the school.",
            "d. Into the school the teacher went quickly at 8: 30 a.m."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 78,
        "question_text": "A container is used to  something.",
        "correct_answer": "d. hold",
        "other_options": [
            "a. find",
            "b. buy",
            "c. make"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 79,
        "question_text": "The military camp was destroyed by the hurricane.  The camp was ruined by      .",
        "correct_answer": "d. a violent storm",
        "other_options": [
            "a. a big bomb",
            "b. an earthquake",
            "c. the enemy"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 80,
        "question_text": "This pill is coated with sugar.",
        "correct_answer": "c. covered",
        "other_options": [
            "a. counted",
            "b. made",
            "d. taken"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 81,
        "question_text": "Every elected official has an obligation to represent the voters.",
        "correct_answer": "a. a duty",
        "other_options": [
            "b. a problem",
            "c. a moral",
            "d. an office"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 82,
        "question_text": "The student picked up his clothes at the laundry.",
        "correct_answer": "c. He got them.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He left them there.",
            "b. He checked them in.",
            "d. He saw them."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 83,
        "question_text": "We can’t drive much farther because we are almost gas.",
        "correct_answer": "d. out of",
        "other_options": [
            "a. out on",
            "b. out for",
            "c. out to"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 84,
        "question_text": "The candidate,by many, decided not to run.",
        "correct_answer": "d. supported",
        "other_options": [
            "a. supporting",
            "b. to support",
            "c. supports"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 85,
        "question_text": "We  here for five months.",
        "correct_answer": "b. have been living",
        "other_options": [
            "a. are living",
            "c. live",
            "d. were living"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 86,
        "question_text": "The letter may in the mail.",
        "correct_answer": "c. be lost",
        "other_options": [
            "a. lost",
            "b. be losing",
            "d. lose"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 87,
        "question_text": ", the meeting went well.",
        "correct_answer": "d. Overall",
        "other_options": [
            "a. Provided",
            "b. In case of",
            "c. In spite of"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 88,
        "question_text": "Hector agreed to drive the car.",
        "correct_answer": "d. He agreed that he would drive the car.",
        "other_options": [
            "a. He agreed that someone should drive the car.",
            "b. He agreed that he had driven the car.",
            "c. He agreed that anyone could drive the car."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 89,
        "question_text": "One great quest of man is for happiness.  It is a fact that money can buy many of the things\nwhich make up happiness; but it is a mistaken idea that wealth, in itself, is a guarantee of\nhappiness. According to this paragraph,     .",
        "correct_answer": "a. money cannot guarantee happiness",
        "other_options": [
            "b. wealth is a curse",
            "c. man’s greatest quest is for riches",
            "d. man is not happy"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 90,
        "question_text": "The instructor was amazed at the students’ progress.",
        "correct_answer": "c. surprised",
        "other_options": [
            "a. happy",
            "b. relieved",
            "d. suspicious"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 91,
        "question_text": "We searched for him throughout the city.",
        "correct_answer": "a. all over",
        "other_options": [
            "b. in part of",
            "c. outside of",
            "d. beside"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 92,
        "question_text": "Do you if I turn on the TV?",
        "correct_answer": "d. mind",
        "other_options": [
            "a. want",
            "b. wish",
            "c. like"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 93,
        "question_text": "is his estimated time of arrival?",
        "correct_answer": "d. What",
        "other_options": [
            "a. Why",
            "b. Who",
            "c. Whose"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 94,
        "question_text": "That movie director has a new film which is his earlier work.",
        "correct_answer": "b. more like",
        "other_options": [
            "a. like most",
            "c. like to",
            "d. as likely"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 95,
        "question_text": "If you stop at the BX,  me some cigarettes.",
        "correct_answer": "a. buy",
        "other_options": [
            "b. would buy",
            "c. should have bought",
            "d. will buy"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 96,
        "question_text": "Barbara’s her job affected her family’s lifestyle tremendously.",
        "correct_answer": "d. losing",
        "other_options": [
            "a. lost",
            "b. was lost",
            "c. was losing"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 97,
        "question_text": "Two different scales are used to measure atmospheric temperatures.  The older Fahrenheit\nscale is used mostly by the general public of the US and certain other countries, while the\nCelsius scale, or centigrade scale, is used by scientists nearly everywhere.  The latter scale\nrecords freezing temperature as 0 degrees. According to this paragraph, the Celsius\nscale       .",
        "correct_answer": "c. registers the freezing point at zero",
        "other_options": [
            "a. measures temperatures in different scales",
            "b. is the same as the Fahrenheit scale",
            "d. is not often used by scientists"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 98,
        "question_text": "Ms. Warren, the newly hired teacher, was asked to speak extemp concerning her\nteaching experiences while in China.",
        "correct_answer": "d. -oraneously",
        "other_options": [
            "a. -oraneity",
            "b. -orary",
            "c. -orize"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 99,
        "question_text": "Joe couldn’t see the car beside him because his vision was poor.",
        "correct_answer": "d. peripheral",
        "other_options": [
            "a. latent",
            "b. rearview",
            "c. occluded"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 100,
        "question_text": "When the continent was first discovered, there were vast tracts of unexplored ……",
        "correct_answer": "d. wilderness",
        "other_options": [
            "a. districts",
            "b. inhabitants",
            "c. livestock"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    }
]